<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Marreply</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1" translatable="false">뉴스피드</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2" translatable="false">견적</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3" translatable="false">커뮤니티</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4" translatable="false">마이페이지</string>
    <string name="action_settings" translatable="false">설정</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newsfeed">NewsfeedActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_login">로그인</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">아이디 및 이메일</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">비밀번호</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">로그인</string>
    <string name="action_register_pw_repeat">비밀번호 확인</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">이메일이 유효하지 않습니다</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">비밀번호가 너무 짧습니다</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">비밀번호가 일치하지 않습니다.</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">아이디는 반드시 입력하셔야 됩니다.</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_bottom">TestBottomActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_mypage">마이페이지</string>
    <string name="title_newsfeed">뉴스피드</string>
    <string name="title_calc">견적</string>
    <string name="title_comm">커뮤니티</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register2">회원가입</string>
    <string name="register_id">아이디</string>
    <string name="regidter_button">가입</string>

    <string name="news_large1">
        "ADAMAS 253\n"
        "\n"
        "카페 아마다스 입니다. 케이블 드라마 마이시크릿호텔에서 유인나씨의"
        "촬영장소로도 유명합니다.위치 자체고 너무 복잡한 곳에 자리잡지 않아서"
        "가장 좋고 독특한 외관 인테리어와 맛있는 브런치 메뉴를 만날 수 있습니다."
        "다이닝 메뉴의  경우 너무 예뻐서 먹기 아깝다는 평이 많습니다."
        "메뉴 외에도 가볍게 커피를 즐기고 이야기꽃 피우기에 안성맞춤입니다.\n"
        "\n"
        "\n"
        "인스퀘어\n"
        "\n"
        "캐쥬얼 다이닝 카페&amp;갤러리 인스퀘어 입니다. 인테리어, 소품쪽에 "
        "관심있는 분들이라면 기대하고 가셔도 좋습니다. 외관에서도 세월의 흔적이"
        "느껴집니다. 헤이리 터줏대감으로 불릴만큼 오랜시간동안 자리를 지키고"
        "있습니다. 날씨가 점점 풀리는 날, 블랙 자몽티 한잔과 달달한 마들렌으로"
        "지나가는 겨울을 즐기기에 충분합니다.\n"
        "\n"
        "\n"
        "콤프카페\n"
        "\n"
        "퍼니쳐카페라고 소개하고 싶습니다. 테라스에는 그네의자도 있어서 연인과"
        "알콩달콩 머물다 가기 좋은 곳입니다. 시그니쳐 커피로 향과 맛을 모두 충족"
        "시킬수 있는 곳으로 옥상에서 연인과 함께 아기자기한 헤이리마을과 "
        "여유로운 브런치로 일주일에 피로를 풀기에 충분합니다.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="news_large2">
        "전주 JTV웨딩 박람회 고객만족도 1위\n\n"

        "본격적인 결혼 준비를 진행하기에 앞서 정말 많은 예비신랑, 신부님이 "
        "실시간 웨딩정보를 얻기 위해 '전주 JTV웨딩 박람회'를 방문해주십니다.\n\n"

        "아무리 인터넷이 발달되서 어떤 정보든 시간과 장소 상관없이 알아볼 수 "
        "있다 하여도 결혼 준비를 완벽하게 진행하기에는 인터넷은 아무래도 "
        "부족한 부분이 있을 수 있기 마련입니다.\n\n"

        "그렇기에 많은 예비신랑, 신부님이 인터넷보다 정확하고 웨딩전문 "
        "플래너와 1:1 상담을 받을수 있는 '전주 JTV웨딩 박람회'를 통해 "
        "결혼준비를 시작하길 선호합니다.\n\n"

        "전주 최대 규모로 진행되는 '전주 JTV웨딩 박람회'같은 경우는 참여하는 "
        "업체 수는 물론이며 준비된 이벤트와 혜택의 폭이 상당합니다. 또한 50쌍 "
        "한정초대로 진행되는 이번 행사같은 경우는 복잡하고 정신없는 웨딩행사가 "
        "아닌 체계적인 시스템을 갖추어 진행하기에 신랑, 신부님은 단 하루 방문 "
        "으로도 결혼준비의 모든 것들을 알고 배워볼 수 있을 것입니다.\n\n"

        "인기 웨딩홀을 시작으로 신상 웨딩드레스 전시. 거기에 강남 청담의 유명 "
        "스튜디오까지 '전주 JTV웨딩 박람회'에 모두 모인다고 하니 볼거리 또한 "
        "넘쳐날 것입니다. 또한 푸짐한 경품 추첨 또한 '전주 JTV웨딩 박람회'의 "
        "즐거움을 한층 높여주는데요. 결혼 준비를 하러 왔다가 선물까지 푸짐하게 "
        "받아가니 집으로 돌아가는 신랑, 신부님의 발걸음은 깃털처럼 가벼울 것입니다.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="news_large3">
"많은 이들에게 사랑받는 2018 신혼여행지 추천 TOP10 \n\n"
""
"1. 코사무이\n\n"
""
"유럽 분위기가 물씬 풍기는 고급 휴양지, 코사무이!\n"
"레오나르도 디카프리오가 출연했던 영화 '더비치' 촬영지로도 유명한 곳입니다.\n"
"푸른 바다와 수려한 경관이 여행자의 마음을 사로잡으며, 신혼여행지로도 명성을"
"떨치고 있습니다. 신혼여행지로 유명해진만큼 리조트와 풀빌라도 다양하게 밀집되어 "
"있으니 여행 만족도가 높은 코사무이에서 행복한 신혼여행 즐겨보세요♥\n\n\n"
""
""
"2. 푸켓\n\n"
""
"태국 남서쪽에 위치한 큰 섬, 푸켓은 아름답고 맑은 해변과 푸른색의 산, 보기만 해도 "
"아름다운 자연 환경을 지니고 있는 곳입니다. 또 대표적인 휴양지로 이미 유명한 곳입니다.\n"
"해양스포츠를 즐기기에도 최적의 장소라서 볼거리 만큼이나 즐길거리인 액티비티도 "
"다양합니다. 프라이빗한 풀빌라, 짜릿한 해양액티비티, 신나는 유흥까지 모두 갖추고 있는 "
"푸켓에서 잊을 수 없는 신혼여행의 추억을 만들어보세요.\n\n\n"
""
""
"3. 하와이\n\n"
""
"관광, 쇼핑 두가지를 다 잡고 싶을 땐 하와이가 신혼여행지로 제격입니다!\n"
"다양한 허니문 여행지가 새롭게 떠오르고 있지만 부동의 1위로 많은 사람들의 지지를 "
"얻고 있는 No.1 신혼여행지 하와이. 에메랄드 빛 바다는 기본으로 볼 수 있고, "
"근사한 자연 경관과 깔끔하고 고급스러운 쇼핑 공간까지, 잠시 브루주아가 된 느낌으로 "
"하와이 곳곳에 발 디뎌보세요! 해양 액티비티를 좋아하는 분이시라면 해변 물놀이, 서핑, "
"스노쿨링 등 액티비티도 마음껏 즐길 수 있어요!\n\n\n"
""
""
"4. 폴리네시아\n\n"
""
"오세아니아 동쪽 해역에 분포하는 수천 개의 섬들을 총칭하여 부르는 폴리네시아.\n"
"TV에 자주 나오기도 하고, 그만큼 아름다운 자연경관을 지니고 있는 곳인데요!\n"
"대표적으로 타히티 섬과 보라보라 섬이 있습니다! 세계에서 가장 아름다운 해변인 "
"보라보라 섬은 특히나 신혼여행 온 부부들이 많습니다. 본섬인 타히티도 마찬가지입니다!\n"
"타국의 휴양 섬과 마찬가지로 폴리네시아 섬 내부에도 프라이빗한 풀빌라와 자연 경관 등 "
"볼거리가 다양하니, 신혼 여행지로 꼭 고민해보세요♥\n\n\n"
""
""
"5. 호주 시드니\n\n"
""
"예비 부부들이 한번 쯤 신혼여행지로 고민해봤을 법한 그곳. 호주 시드니입니다!\n"
"귀여운 왈라루가 뛰노는 시드니는 사계절 여행하기 좋은 곳이죠!\n"
"아름다운 시드니 관광과 때묻지 않은 호주의 자연경관을 찾는 여행자들이 늘면서 "
"온리 휴양 보단 관광+휴양 두가지 모두를 원하는 신혼부부들이 많이 찾고 있습니다 :)\n\n\n"
""
""
"6. 체코\n\n"
""
"허니문 스냅으로 이미 유명한 체코. 로맨틱, 달콤함, 낭만 그 자체라고 할 수 있죠!\n"
"체코로 신혼여행 가게 되면 유럽의 느낌을 피부로 직접 느껴도 보고, 고풍스로운 "
"분위기에서 맛있는 식사도 즐길 수 있습니다. 방문하는 관광지마다 분위기가 어마어마해서 "
"발 닿는 곳 마다 포토존일 것입니다. '남는건 사진 뿐이다'라는 말처럼 좋은 사진, "
"예쁜 사진도 많이 남기고 오세요♥\n\n\n"
""
""
"7. 이탈리아\n\n"
""
"관광지 탐방, 미술관 방문 등 일반 여행처럼 관광이 목적인 신혼부부에게 제격인 여행지가 "
"여기 있습니다, 바로 이탈리아!\n"
"유럽여행에 도전하지 못하고 있다가 신형여행을 빌미로 유럽여행에 한 번쯤 도전하고 싶다면 "
"그 무엇보다도 이탈리아에 방문해 보시는 것을 추천드립니다.\n"
"휴양지는 추후 태교 여행으로도 많이 방문하시기 때문에 장기간 여행이 어려우신 분들이라면 "
"일반 여행처럼 관광을 즐기기 제격인 이탈리아를 많이 찾으십니다.\n"
"이탈리아 내에도 로마, 베니스, 피렌체 등등 다양한 도시, 다양한 매력이 공존하기 때문에 "
"원하는 지역을 골라서 여행하시면 좋을 것 같습니다!\n\n\n"
""
""
"8. 칸쿤\n\n"
""
"뜨고 있는,아니 이미 뜰만큼 떠버린 신혼여행지! 멕시코 칸쿤, 생각만 해도 시원한 바다가 "
"떠올라요. 프라이빗한 풀빌라는 물론 올인클루시브 리조트로 숙박부터 액티비티, 유흥까지 "
"전부 즐길 수 있는 곳이 바로 멕시코 칸쿤이죠! 멕시코는 나라 자체는 위험하지만 칸쿤 지역만큼 "
"최고의 치안과 최적의 자연 환경을 유지하고 있기 때문에 걱정 없이 여행을 즐길 수 있어요!\n\n\n"
""
""
"9. 캐나다\n\n"
""
"아름다운 자연만큼이나 도시에서의 관광도 볼거리,즐길거리가 다양한 캐나다! 록키 산맥으로도 "
"이미 많은 사람들에게 입소문 나 있는 캐나다는 도시에서도, 휴양지에서도 어느 곳에서도 "
"캐나다에서만 느낄수 있는 고유의 분위기 속에서 행복한 신혼여행을 즐기다 올수 있어요!\n"
"벤쿠버,퀘벡,빅토리아 등 여행을 즐길 수 있는 도시가 다양하니 꼭 즐겨보시길 보랍니다 :)\n\n\n"
""
""
"10. 피지\n\n"
""
"휴양과 레저를 동시에 즐길 수 있는 피지. 아름다운 경관 또한 만나볼 수 있어 여행 내내 "
"행복감을 만끽할 수 있어요. 단독공간에서 둘만의 여행을 즐기고 싶은 분들이라면 피지여행을 "
"강력 추천하는데요! 피지 한 곳만 여행하는 것이 심심할 것 같으면 다른 나를르 묶어서 패키지로 "
"다녀오는 경우도 있다고 하니 피지 여행, 고민 말고 고고싱! 하세요!"
"
    </string>
    <string name="card_calc1">
        "복잡한 결혼 준비,\n좋은 전문가를 만나는 게 시작입니다"
    </string>
    <string name="card_calc2">
        "결혼 계획 작성 후\n원하시는 전문가에게 편하게 문의하세요."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_nav_drawer_test">NavDrawerTestActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
